<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | AMI - Automatic Misogyny Identification - EVALITA 2020</title>
    <link>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/fersini_elisabetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/fersini_elisabetta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elisabetta Fersini&lt;/strong&gt; is currently Associate Professor in Computer Science at the 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.unimib.it&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;University of Milano-Bicocca&lt;/a&gt;, Italy. Her research is mainly focused on machine learning for natural language processing. She has (co-)authored more than 60 peer-reviewed publications and served as reviewer in top journals (e.g. Information Science, Knowledge and Information Systems, Expert Systems with Applications, Artificial Intelligence).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was principal investigator in projects funded for data analytics and the organizer of the special session about Emotion and Sentiment in Intelligent Systems and Big Social Data Analysis at the IEEE-DSAA in 2015 and 2016. She was one of the organizers of the task on misogyny identification at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/view/ibereval-2018&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ibereval&lt;/a&gt; and 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.evalita.it/2018&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Evalita 2018&lt;/a&gt;, and one of the organizers of the HatEval Task 5 at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aclweb.org/anthology/S19-2007/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;SemEval 2019&lt;/a&gt;. She is member of the editorial board of Information Processing and Management, Editor of the Book “Sentiment Analysis in Social Networks” (2016) and Guest Editor for the Special Issue Data Analytics and Optimization (Elsevier).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/nozza_debora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/nozza_debora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debora Nozza&lt;/strong&gt; is a Postdoctoral Research Fellow at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https:%5c%5cwww.bocconi.it/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Bocconi University&lt;/a&gt;. Her research interests mainly focus on Natural Language Processing, specifically on the detection and counter-acting of hate speech and algorithmic bias on Social Media data in multilingual context.
She was Area Chair at the 14th Women in 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wimlworkshop.org/2019/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Machine Learning Workshop (WiML)&lt;/a&gt; at NeurIPS 2019 and active member of the Milan Women in Machine Learning and Data Science community.
She was one of the organizers of the task on Automatic Misogyny Identification (AMI) at 
&lt;a href=&#34;%5curl%7bhttp://www.evalita.it/2018%7d&#34;&gt;Evalita 2018&lt;/a&gt;, and one of the organizers of the HatEval Task 5 at [SemEval 2019]((\url{http://alt.qcri.org/semeval2019/}) on multilingual detection of hate speech against immigrants and women in Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/rosso_paolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amievalita2020.github.io/authors/rosso_paolo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paolo Rosso&lt;/strong&gt; is full professor at the Universitat Politecnica de Valencia, Spain where he is also member of the PRHLT research center. His research interests focus mainly on author profiling, irony detection, fake reviews detection, plagiarism detection, and recently hate speech and fake news detection. Since 2009 he has been involved in the organisation of PAN benchmark activities at CLEF and at FIRE evaluation forums, mainly on plagiarism / text reuse detection and author profiling. At SemEval he has been co-organiser of shared tasks on sentiment analysis of figurative language in Twitter (2015), and on multilingual detection of hate speech against immigrants and women in Twitter (2019). He is co-ordinator of the activities of IberLEF evaluation forum. He has been PI of national and international research projects funded by EC and U.S. Army Research Office. At the moment, in collaboration with Carnegie Mellon University, he is involved in a project funded by Qatar National Research Fund on author profiling for cyber-security. He serves as deputy steering committee chair for the CLEF conference and as associate editor for the Information Processing &amp;amp; Management journal. He has been chair of *SEM-2015, and organisation chair of CERI-2012, CLEF-2013 and EACL-2017. He is the author of 400+ papers, published in journals, book chapters, conference and workshop proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
